

# CONTACT

😲 🛮 Baku, Azerbaijan



+79104623906 (What's app only)



nikita8192@ya.ru



In linkedin.com/in/nikita-nefedov

### **SKILLS**

- Data analysis
- MS Excel
- Python
- SQL
- STATA
- Financial audit
- Analytical reports
- Presentations
- MS Powerpoint
- Tableau
- Political science
- **Public opinion**
- Scientific research

### **LANGUAGES**

Russian: native

English: fluent

# Nikita Nefedov

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Nikita is an initiative, responsible and time-managing person with a range of practical and theoretical experience in the data analysis and financial control. Academically qualified in politics and public opinion analysis. Highly motivated for group leadership and project initiatives, provide support and elaborate new processes through ongoing projects.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Advisor of an expert and analytical department

2/2021 - 11/2022

Government of Moscow - Head Control Derictorate - Moscow, Russia

- Data analysis and financial audit.
- Implementation of state control in the financial and budgetary sphere, procurement, social sector (healthcare, urban construction, education).
- Conduction of anti-corruption and anti-monopoly investigations.
- Evaluation of the effectiveness of the disposal of organizations of their budgetary funds.

10/2020 - 12/2020 Intern

Moscow City Innovation Agency - Moscow, Russia

- Consulting in the field of technology development and innovative entrepreneurship.
- Monitoring of the innovation market and development of plans for cooperation with key partners.
- Organization of industry forums.

Volunteer 4/2019 - 6/2019

**UN Online Volunteering service** – Colchester, England

Participated in development of Tanzanian infrastructure, managed IT software.

## **EDUCATION**

Master of Arts: Public Opinion and Political Behaviour (with distinction)

2018 - 2019

University of Essex - Colchester, England

- Average mark: 1
- Dissertation project has a first-class mark
- Qualification modules include: Public Opinion and Political Behaviour, Quantitative Political analysis, Conflict Resolution, International Negotiations, Theory and **Explanation in Political Science**

**Bachelor of Arts:** Political Science

2015 - 2018

University of Essex - Colchester, England

- Average mark: 2.1
- Qualification modules include: Scientific and Political Analysis, Authoritarianism and Corruption, Philosophy, British Politics, Parties and Elections analysis, Politics of the Middle East, Discourse Analysis, European Union institutions and policies
- President of the Russian Society (2 terms)

Foundation Degree: Politics University of Essex - Colchester, England 2014 - 2015